A Guide to the Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Electric and Power Company Records, 1849-ca. 1995
Library of Virginia
37345
32 cubic feet and approximately 510 volumes
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Virginia Electric and Power Company, Richmond, Virginia in May 2000.
Historical Information
The Virginia Electric and Power Company, now known as Dominion Virginia Power, comprises approximately 250 subsidiary companies which were purchased or merged into the company over its 220 year existence. For the purposes of this description, Virginia Electric and Power Company will be shortened to its acronym and pseudonym "VEPCO." The company became known as the Virginia Electric and Power Company in 1925 when its two principal subsidiaries, the Spotsylvania Power Company of Fredericksburg and the Virginia Railway and Power Company, merged. To facilitate description, "VEPCO" will be used to describe the company both before and after this merger.
In 1787, the Virginia General Assembly established the Appomattox Trustees, a corporation whose original purpose was clearing, improving and extending the navigation along the Appomattox River so that rum and tobacco might be hauled into the Virginia highlands from the Tidewater and Hampton Roads. Since the founding of this corporation, more than 250 subsidiary companies founded for various and sundry enterprises as water power, real estate, horse shoe manufacturing, ice making, coal mining, laundry, railway and trolley service, ferry service and street lighting have joined the corporate ancestry of VEPCO. Like the Appomattox Trustees the earliest subsidiaries of VEPCO generally organized to focus on the development of canals and water power in Virginia. By the mid-19th century, however, the arrival of passenger railways and electricity, especially in urban areas, had displaced water travel and power as the focus of VEPCO subsidiary companies. Many VEPCO subsidiaries flourished during the late 19th and early 20th century after the appearance of urban electrical streetcars.
On 29 June 1909, the Virginia Railway and Power Company was incorporated to acquire three of the largest rail companies in Richmond. This was the corporate birthday and the real beginning of the Virginia Electric and Power Company. During the 1910's the company operated streetcars in four cities under complex and inflexible franchises. After World War I streetcar fares failed to adjust to meet increased cost demand. In the early 1920's city, state and national government and courts were asked to take charge of the crisis. Ultimately the Virginia State Corporation Commission took jurisdiction over public transportation and electrical companies, but failed to address the fare issue. As a result by the mid-1920's, streetcar and electrical companies had shifted their business pendulum to focus principally on the distribution of electrical power. For the next three quarters of a century, this power company continued to consolidate smaller companies and increase the size of its power grid throughout Virginia and Northern North Carolina.
Scope and Content
Records, 1849-ca. 1995, of the Virginia Electric and Power Company (VEPCO) consisting of advertisements including posters and broadsides, correspondence, journals, ledgers, legal files, memorabilia, minute books, photographs, plats, publications including booklets and pamphlets, scrapbooks, for the company and its subsidiary companies.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically and chronologically with folder contents in reverse chronological order. Organized into the following ten series: Series I. General Counsel/Vice President Files (Subseries A. Correspondence, Subseries B. Legal Files, Subseries C. Financial Files, Subseries D. Personnel Files, Subseries E. Annual Reports, Subseries F. Jamestown Exposition Files), Series II. Treasurer's Files (Subseries A. Customer Accounts, Subseries B. Dividend and Stock Accounts), Series III. VEPCO Relief Association Files, Series IV. Publications, Series V. Right-of-Way Plats, Series VI. Photographs, Series VII. Advertisements, Series VIII. Scrapbooks, Series IX. Memorabilia, Series X. Minute books and ledgers.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Virginia Electric and Power Company, Collection of miscellaneous brochures, ca. 1950 (LVA Accession 38155). Also see library collection for various printed items.
Contents List
- General Counsel and Vice President Files, 1887-1942, 14.4 cubic feet (Box 1-32)
  These are the files kept by the General Counsel, who also was a vice president of the company. The majority of this series contains legal files, but there is also material in this series from other departments and pertaining to other matters that required executive decisions. The General Counsel's papers remain together as they were filed by the company; however, the folders have been alphabetically rearranged according to subject.
  Alphabetically and then chronologically with folder contents arranged in reverse chronological order. This maintains the original organization incorporated by the company.
  - Correspondence, 1914-1925, .9 cubic feet (Box 1-2)
    Principally consists of the general business correspondence of the General Counsel and Vice President E. Randolph Williams. This business correspondence dates from 1921-1925 and generally does not refer to specific legal cases as is the case with the legal files in Subseries B. These correspondence files concern various business and legal matters brought to the attention of the general counsel by interoffice staff, other business persons and governmental officials. At the end of this series is a folder containing correspondence, 1914-1919, in reference to articles that appeared in Public Service, the VEPCO newsletter.
    Alphabetically and then chronologically with folder contents arranged in reverse chronological order according to the system used by the company.
    - Correspondence - A, 1920-1924 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - B, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - B, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - B, 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - C, 1920-1924 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - D, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - E and F, 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - G, 1919-1922 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - G, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - H-J, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - H-J, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - H-J, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence - H-J, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence - H-J, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - K-L, 1920-1925 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence - M, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence - M, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - M, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - M, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - M, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence - M, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence - N-O, 1921-1923 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - P-Q, 1919-1924 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - R, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - R, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - R, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - R, 1923-1925 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence - S, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence - S, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence - S, 1922-1924 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence - T-V, 1920 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence - T-V, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence - T-V, 1922-1924 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence - Y-Z, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence in reference to articles that appeared in Public Service, the VEPCO newsletter, 1914-1919 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Legal Files, 1903-1942, 11.475 cubic feet (Box 3-27)
    Contains correspondence and legal and case files including legal briefs, generally exchanged between the General Counsel, VEPCO attorneys and claims agents in the Legal Department, VEPCO executives, opposing counsels and litigants, other businesses and business persons, and government and court officials. Many of the cases concern personal injury, fatal error, and property lawsuits caused by accidents on or with streetcars. Other files pertain to streetcar operation and fares. There are also legal documents including deeds and contracts concerning the purchase and transfer of property right-of-ways, property disputes, and the development of infrastructure in Richmond and Norfolk including street paving, streetcar lines and railways, water and gas lines, and power grids. Other legal files including most notably the dense case of Charles Hall Davis concern lawsuits in reference to stock and dividend disputes. A small amount of files also concerns deferred classification for war military service by VEPCO employees. At the end of this subseries are case summaries and lists, 1921-1923, arranged chronologically by the company.
    Alphabetically by case name or legal subject and then chronologically with folder contents arranged in reverse chronological order.
    - Cases: General - A, 1919-1924 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Aaron, T. R., case of, 1916-1919 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Abady, Samuel A., case of, 1920-1923 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Abdoo, Amelia, case of, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Adams Express Company, case of, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Addenbrock, J. A., case of, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Addison, Fred J., case of, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Agey, T. G., case of, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Aigner, Louis, case of, 1920-1923 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Albemarle Paper Company, State Corporation Commission, complaint, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Allen, Bessie T., case of, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - American Chemical Company, case of, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - American Labor Legislation Review, May-June 1915 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - American Labor Legislation Review, December 1915 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - American Locomotive Company, agreement and contract to provide electric current, 1904 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - American Railway Express Company, case of, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Amos, Ruby, case of, 1921-1923 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - "Anderson To Go To Greece" ( Norfolk Ledger-Dispatch article), 1918 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Anderson, R. L., case of, 1916 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Anderson, Richard Lynn, case of, 1921-1922 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Annuzato, August and Hoffer Brothers, cases of, 1917-1918 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Applefeld, William B., case of, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Archer, Gertrude A., case of, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Archer, John, case of, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Arluck, H., case of, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Armistead Avenue (Norfolk) track extension, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Arnold, Esther, case of, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Arnold, J. W., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Arrington, Lewis, Jr., case of, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Arrow Laundry, case of, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Askew, Lonnie, case of, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Askew, W. S., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Aten, W. E., case of, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad Company and Western Union Telegraph Company, contract, 1910-1912 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, Richmond property transaction, January-March 1916 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, Richmond property transaction, April-May 1916 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Austin, Nellie, case of, 1920 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Ayres, Addie, case of, 1918 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Cases: General - B, April 1922-November 1923 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Cases: General - B, January-March 1924 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - American Chemical Company, case of, April-May 1924 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Cases: General - B, June 1924 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Cases: General - B, July-December 1924 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Cases: General - B, January-April 1925 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Cases: General - B, February 1926 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Bachman, G., case of, 1919 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Bacon, Jennie (administrator of Monroe Bacon), case of, 1922 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Bailey, Garnett A., case of, 1916-1919 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Baird, Edwin T., case of, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Baker, Julius S., case of, 1917 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (briefs), 1904-1907 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (briefs), April 1920 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (briefs), May 1920 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (briefs), June 1920 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (briefs), October 1920 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (briefs), November 1920 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (briefs), November 1921 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (correspondence), June-October 1921 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (correspondence), November 1921-September 1922 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Bankers Trust Company and Thomas O'Connor, et. al., case of (correspondence), October 1922-July 1923 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Bankrupt companies' claims cases, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Banks, Jacob and John L. Peter, cases of, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Banks, Joseph and Mary E. Maher, cases of, 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Banks, Maggie, case of, 1922-1925 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Banwarth, C. D., case of, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Barnard, John, case of, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Barton Heights (Richmond), contract for current for electric pumping purposes, 1911 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Barton Heights (Richmond), property dispute, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Baskette, C. D., case of, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Batts, L., case of, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Baxter, Garrett, case of, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Baydush, B., case of (B1676), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Baydush, B., case of (B1678), 1919 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Bay Shore, litigation and attorney's fees, 1907-1914 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Bay Shore Terminal Company, track removal of Crawford and First Streets (Norfolk), 1912 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Beaman, W. W., case of, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Beard, C. W., case of, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Bedsar, C. A., case of, 1915 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Bedsar, Charles A., case of, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Begar, H. A., case of, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Bell, Dempsey C., case of, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Bell, Emma V., case of, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Bellman, W. M., case of, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Bellwood, James, contract of, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Belvin, Mattie, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Bennett, E. E., case of, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Bennett, L. R., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Benton, B. B., case of, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Berkley Line easement agreement, 1914 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Berlin, Lewis, case of, 1915-1916 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Berman, Joseph, case of, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Berry, O. H., case of, 1921-1922 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Bethel, Ozeta, case of, 1920-1921 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Beverly, Frank, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Beville, Frank W., case of, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Bidgood, Bessie D., case of, 1915-1916 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Billups, E. L., case of, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Bionda, Nunziato, case of, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Black customers' line extension request, 1914-1915 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Black, George H., case of, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Black, Martha, case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Blackwell, Hannie, case of, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Blackwell, Otis Lee, case of, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Blackwell, Robert and William Betts and Mary Hart, cases of, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Blair and Mayo, Westhampton (Richmond) lot dedication, 1912-1913 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Block system steam-heating services, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Blount, John, case of, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Blount, William, case of, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Bonney, A. J., case of, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Boone, Minnie, case of, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Borum, William Hodges, case of, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Bosher, Lewis H., case of, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Bowen, L. H., case of, 192 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Bowman, W. E., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Bradley, A. J., case of Archer's Island land grant, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Bradshaw, John E., case of, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Branch, L. T., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Braxton, Barney, case of, 1917-1918 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Brenner, I. L., case of, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Brickhouse, Edward L., case of, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Briggs, G. S., case of, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Bright, J. E., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Briggs, L. O., case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Brittain, Robert E. L., case of, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Broadhurst, Robert, case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Broad Street (Richmond) track reconstruction and paving, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Broad Street (Richmond) West End line extension, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Brooke, I., case of, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Brooks, F. P., case of, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Brooks, Mary, case of, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Brooks, S. H., case of, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Broudy, M., case of, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Brown, Betsy, case of, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Brown, Julia, case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Brown, Julia A., case of, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Brown, Julian, case of, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Brownrigg, L. M., case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Bryan Park (Richmond) line extension, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Buchanan, Charlotte A., case of, 1916-1917 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Buchanan, Roland, case of, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Bullock, B. F., case of, 1921, 1925 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Bunting, Helen Agnes, case of, 1916-1917 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Bunting, Robert, case of, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Burden, Jerry, case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Burk, A. R., case of, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Burk, Gladys, case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Burnett, O. L., case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Butler, J. T., case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Butler, T., case of, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Bybee, Harry R., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Cases: General - C, 1921-1923 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Cases: General - C, January-June 1924 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Cases: General - C, July 1924-April 1925 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Cahen, Sallie E., case of, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Calhoun Falls Water Power proposition, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Callis, Bertha Ray, case of, 1917, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Calvert, Mary E., case of, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Camp, Camp and Beadles, case of, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Caplan, I., case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Caprio, Mary, case of, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Caprio, Rosa, case of, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Carnahan, A. P., case of, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Carroll, Daisy, case of, 1920-1922 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Cassell, Jane, case of, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Cauthorne, N. C., case of, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Cavan, J. R., case of (B2157), 1921 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Cavan, J. R., case of (B2151), 1921, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - C. D. Mahane and Son, case of, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Chaffin Street (Richmond) property transaction, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Chapman, C. E., case of, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Chapman, E. E., case of, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 78a)
    - Chatman, Kate, case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Cheatham, E. T., case of, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Chenault, Laura L. (administrator of J. R. Chenault), case of, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Chenault, W. T. (administrator of Charles H. Beadle), case of, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Cherry, Estelle, case of, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cherry, John B., case of, 1918-1920 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Cherry, John B., case of, n. d. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Cherry, John B., case of, n. d. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway, James River land dispute, case of, 1915-1917 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway, James River land dispute, case of, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Chesson, J. S., case of, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Chesterman, R. L., case of, 1922-1923 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Childress, Elizabeth S., case of, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Childrey, Roy, case of, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Chinn, Cynthia, case of, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, 1907-1908 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, 1909-1911 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, 1913-1914 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, January-February 1917 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, 1-15 March 1917 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, 16-31 March 1917 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, May 1917 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, June 1917 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, July 1917 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, August-November 1917 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, December 1917 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, January 1918 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, February 1918 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, March 1918 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, April-May 1918 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, July 1918 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates, December 1918-June 1919 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates (charts), 1917 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - City Gas Company of Norfolk, state case against to raise rates (publications and briefs), 1917 (Box 7, Folder 11a)
    - Clarke, Victoria and Louis I. Sherman, cases of, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Clarkson, Annie Amelia, case of, 1922-1923 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Cline, James H., case of, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 14)